Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; 105120
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 151673
    - Project accounting for "Fanzine", 1995; cuid7627; 153962 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Publishing rights, 1994 - 1995; cuid7628; 151914 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - RH+Bothered #2 archive, 1992-1995; cuid7629; 160521 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      Removable Hard Drive has been moved to Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage.
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7630; 151674 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 138329
    - Flier - Red Hot + Bothered 1, [1995]; cuid7631; 161126 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Fliers - Red Hot + Bothered 2, [1995]; cuid7632; 161127 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Invitation to release of Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid7633; 161132 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid7634; 161129 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Press clippings, 1995 - 1996; cuid7635; 138330 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Press releases, 1995; cuid7636; 161917 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Stickers - Red Hot + Bothered, [n.d.]; cuid7637; 161128 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Table tent - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid7638; 161125 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material, 160532
    - Slides (color): Red Hot & Bothered #2 zine cover, 1995; cuid7639; 160535 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161130
    - Red Hot + Bothered; Kinetic Records, 1995; cuid7640; 161133 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Red Hot + Bothered CD insert (back), 1995; cuid7641; 161131 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Series VIII: The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip, 139218
  This series encompasses both "The Beat Experience" CD-ROM/Video and "Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip" enhanced audio CD.
  Released by WAX TRAX / TVT in 1996, "Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip" was an offshoot of The Beat Experience, a project exploring the legacy of the Beat generation produced by The Red Hot Organization in association with the Whitney Museum of American Art. "The Beat Experience" CD-ROM combines text, jazz, underground films and visual art to anthologize the period, while "The Beat Experience" video is an hour TV show that presents the era in a contemporary edit of archive filmclips, sound bites, music and abstract imagery.
  (Reference: Offbeat: A Red Hot Happening flier; http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 151675
    - Adamson, Barry, 1995; cuid7642; 153909 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Advances from Wax Trax Records (label) and Voyager (distributor), 1995 - 1996; cuid7643; 153900 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7644; 151748 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Baraka, Amiri / DJ Spooky, cuid7645; 156574 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Beat Disk (contents: Budget.xls, Footage.xls, flmcred.doc & VHS list), [n.d.]; cuid7646; 157297 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      TDK micro floppy disk
    - Billing: Mastering, Editing, 1995 - 1996; cuid7647; 153912 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Budget notes, [n.d.]; cuid7648; 153930 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Budget / Paid invoices (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7649; 156888 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Carney, Ray, 1995; cuid7650; 157298 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Clearances, 1995 - 1997; cuid7651; 153920 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Clearances: Labels, Artists, Publish, 1995 - 1996; cuid7652; 153922 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Contracts, CD-ROM & Film: Outstanding, 1995; cuid7653; 153935 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1995 - 1996; cuid7654; 153959 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Credits, 1995; cuid7655; 153932 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Distribution, 1995 - 1997; cuid7656; 153934 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - DJ Krush, 1995 - 1996; cuid7657; 153916 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Emergency Broadcast Network, 1995; cuid7658; 153913 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Expenses: Party/Event, 1996; cuid7659; 153915 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Footage (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7660; 157040 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Footage, 1995; cuid7661; 157232 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Laika / My Bloody Valentine, 1995 - 1996; cuid7662; 153914 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - McBride, Christian / DJ Krazy, 1995; cuid7663; 153918 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Masters, 1995 - 2001; cuid7664; 153924 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Meat Beat Manifesto, 1995; cuid7665; 153917 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Music - Masters, 1993-1995; cuid7666; 157300 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Music - Publishers, 1995; cuid7667; 157301 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Music / Spoken word, [n.d.]; cuid7668; 157302 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Ndegocello, Me'Shell, 1995; cuid7669; 153911 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Nicosia, Gerald, 1995; cuid7670; 157299 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Notes, "John's", 1995; cuid7671; 153928 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Notes, Lisa [Hacken]'s (Research coordinator), 1995; cuid7672; 153933 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Offbeat Archive, [n.d.]; cuid7673; 160520 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Paid Invoices (Restricted), 1995; cuid7674; 156889 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Pending / Money received, 1995; cuid7675; 156890 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Publishing, 1995 - 1996; cuid7676; 153921 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Red Hot and Beat, 1995; cuid7677; 160524 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Royalty statement, 1996 - 1997; cuid7678; 154032 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Shapero, Alyson (Marketing consultant) (Restricted), 1996; cuid7679; 153926 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Skylab, 1996; cuid7680; 153919 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Stills, 1995; cuid7681; 156937 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Includes listing of images to appear on CD-ROM and photocopies of two Dennis Hopper images. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for said images.
    - Stills, 1995-1996; cuid7682; 156942 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Includes photocopies of 11 images featuring Kerouac, Ginsberg, Burroughs and more. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for images appearing on CD-ROM.
    - Synchronization licenses, 1995 - 1996; cuid7683; 153925 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Text, 1995-1996; cuid7684; 156891 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Includes text and images to appear on CD-ROM. Also includes correspondence and agreements to obtain permission rights for said text and images.
    - Text, 1995-1996; cuid7685; 156936 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - TVT Records, 1996; cuid7686; 153891 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Video tracking log, 1995 - 1996; cuid7687; 151676 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - The Voyager Company, 1996 - 1997; cuid7688; 153892 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Wax Trax Records / TVT Records (label), 1995 - 1996; cuid7689; 153927 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 139219
    - Fliers for "Offbeat: A Red Hot Happening" and "The Beat Experience", cuid7690; 153856 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Mousepads labeled "BEATPAD" featuring Sue Coe drawing, 1995; cuid7691; 153858 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Postcard invitations to exhibition of work by Gary Panter and David Sandlin "to celebrate the release of THE BEAT EXPERIENCE CD-ROM/VIDEO and OFFBEAT ENHANCED AUDIO CD", c.a. 1996; cuid7692; 153859 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Press clippings, 1995-1996; cuid7693; 139220 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Press clippings, compilation of 1996, cuid7694; 153929 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Press release, 1995; cuid7695; 153931 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Promotional: The Beat Experience, 1995; cuid7696; 153855 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Stickers, [n.d.]; cuid7697; 153852 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material, 151754
    - Negatives: Sue Coe artwork, 1995; cuid7698; 151755 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Slides (black and white): Mostly portraits of artistes, cuid7699; 160526 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Slides (color): Offbeat and The Beat Experience covers, cuid7700; 160528 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 153850
    - The Beat Experience, 1996; cuid7701; 153857 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      Compact disc read-only memory
    - The Beat Experience, 1995; cuid7702; 153853 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Offbeat: A Red Hot Sound Trip, 1996; cuid7703; 153854 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Enhanced audio compact disc
- Series IX: America Is Dying Slowly, 138334
  America Is Dying Slowly was released in 1996 by Eastwest Records America. It features hip hop producers and rappers who had not previously worked together. (Reference: http://redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 145315
    - 8Ball & MJG, 1996; cuid7704; 156785 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - America@ (RHO#7), 1994-1996; cuid7705; 160500 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      SyQuest 45 MB Removable Hard Disk
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7706; 151702 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Biz Markie, 1996; cuid7707; 156770 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Brian, 1996; cuid7708; 156752 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Buckwild, 1995-1996; cuid7709; 156772 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Cashflow/budget, 1992; cuid7710; 145316 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996; cuid7711; 153923 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996; cuid7712; 161944 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Clearances, 1995-1996; cuid7713; 156760 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Common Sense, 1995-1996; cuid7714; 156773 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Contact info, [n.d.]; cuid7715; 156715 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Contract copies, 1995-1996; cuid7716; 156764 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Coolio (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7717; 156774 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - De La Soul (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7718; 156776 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Development budget, 1992; cuid7719; 147555 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Diamond D (Restricted), 1995; cuid7720; 156778 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Domino, 1996; cuid7721; 156784 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Elektra, 1994-1996; cuid7722; 160499 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Expenses, 1995-1996; cuid7723; 156753 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Expenses, 1995-1996; cuid7724; 156767 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Expenses: Recording sessions, 1996; cuid7725; 153889 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Famous Artists Agency, Inc.: Checks from De La Soul/Fishbone/Goodie Mob tour, 1997; cuid7726; 155302 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Fat Joe, 1996; cuid7727; 156787 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Financial statements, 1996-1998; cuid7728; 153973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The Jungle Brothers, 1995; cuid7729; 156788 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Kool G Rap, 1995-1996; cuid7730; 156790 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Label contracts, 1995-1996; cuid7731; 156756 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - The Lost Boyz, 1995-1996; cuid7732; 156793 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mac Mall (Restricted), 1996; cuid7733; 156796 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Masta Ace (Restricted), 1995; cuid7734; 156798 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - MC Lyte (Restricted), 1995; cuid7735; 156800 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Mobb Deep (Restricted), 1995; cuid7736; 156801 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Money Boss Players (Restricted), 1995; cuid7737; 156871 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - O.C., 1996; cuid7738; 156872 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Organized Konfusion (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7739; 156874 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Paid bills, 1998-1999; cuid7740; 157604 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Panasonic TV commercial, 1993; cuid7741; 147714 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Prince Paul, 1995-1996; cuid7742; 156880 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Producer contracts, 1995-1996; cuid7743; 156755 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Publishing, 1995-1996; cuid7744; 156762 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Red Hot # 18, 1993-1996; cuid7745; 160517 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Return to Helene Silverman / Final "America is Dying Slowly" Artwork, 1994-1996; cuid7746; 160497 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Royalties: "I Breaks 'Em Off" / "The Hustle", 1996-1997; cuid7747; 153972 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - RZA, 1995-1996; cuid7748; 156881 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Samples, 1995-1996; cuid7749; 156766 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Session reports (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7750; 153969 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Skadanks, 1995-1996; cuid7751; 156882 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Special Ed, 1995; cuid7752; 156883 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Spice 1, 1996; cuid7753; 156884 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Usless, 1995-1996; cuid7754; 156754 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Video expenses, 1995-1996; cuid7755; 156886 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7756; 151677 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Wu-Tang Clan, 1995-1996; cuid7757; 156885 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 138336
    - Condoms - America is Dying Slowly, 1996; cuid7758; 151834 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Flier ad for "America is Dying Slowly" record release party, 1996; cuid7759; 151833 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Press clippings, 1996; cuid7760; 138337 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Press clippings, 1996; cuid7761; 162253 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Promos & Show, [n.d.]; cuid7762; 151815 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 151812
    - America Is Dying Slowly; EastWest Records America, 1996; cuid7763; 151827 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - America Is Dying Slowly; EastWest Records America, 1996; cuid7764; 151813 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Series X: Red Hot + Rio, 138332
  Red Hot + Rio was released by VERVE ANTILLES in 1996 and is a tribute to the Bossa Nova sound, with a focus on compositions by Antonio Carlos Jobim. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 151682
    - Advance from PolyGram Records, Inc., 1995; cuid7765; 153901 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Airto / Flora Purim, 1994-1996; cuid7766; 156613 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Artist agreements, 1994-1997; cuid7767; 156589 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7768; 151747 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "The Bachelor" soundtrack, 1999-2000; cuid7769; 156561 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Banana Republic - paid bills, 1998-1999; cuid7770; 157637 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Banana Republic sync, 1999; cuid7771; 156602 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Banana Republic's "Chinos" television campaign, 1999; cuid7772; 156600 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Bjork + Eumir Deodato, 1995-1996; cuid7773; 156626 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bravo Company, 1996-1997; cuid7774; 156591 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Brazil II, 1995-1996; cuid7775; 156710 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Carlinhos, 1995-1996; cuid7776; 156632 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Budget and reimbursements from PolyGram Records (label) - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve, 1996; cuid7777; 161099 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Byrne, David, 1995-1997; cuid7778; 156614 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Cazuza: Som Livre, 1995-1996; cuid7779; 156633 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Chico Science / Goldie Co Production, 1996; cuid7780; 156611 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Record labels, 1996 - 1999; cuid7781; 153956 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Crystal Waters (Restricted), 1996; cuid7782; 156610 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - DJ Soul Slinger, 1996; cuid7783; 156704 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Everything but the Girl, 1995-1996; cuid7784; 156668 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Everything but the Girl, 1995-1996; cuid7785; 156712 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Évora, Cesária, 1996; cuid7786; 156628 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Foreign sales breakdown, 1997; cuid7787; 153968 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Gil, Gilberto, 1993-1996; cuid7788; 156645 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Gilberto, Bebel, 1996; cuid7789; 156616 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hotoda, Goh, 1996; cuid7790; 156651 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Incognito, 1996-1997; cuid7791; 156652 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Invoices (Restricted), 1996; cuid7792; 153903 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Jobim, Antonio Carlos, 1994; cuid7793; 156612 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Label agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7794; 156588 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Licensing, 1996-1998; cuid7795; 156560 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Mad Professor, 1996; cuid7796; 156653 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Mathewman, S., 1996; cuid7797; 156701 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Maxwell (Restricted), 1996; cuid7798; 156654 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Michael, George, 1995-1996; cuid7799; 156634 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Money Mark, 1996; cuid7800; 156656 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Monte, Marisa, 1995-1996; cuid7801; 156615 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - MTV Brasil, 1996-1999; cuid7802; 156559 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Nascimento, Milton, 1995-1997; cuid7803; 156655 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - P.M. Dawn + Flora Purim, 1995-1996; cuid7804; 156657 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Profit and loss statement, 1997; cuid7805; 154162 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Promotional CD collaboration with Mossimo and Details magazine, 1997; cuid7806; 156601 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Publishing, 1995-1997; cuid7807; 156587 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Red Hot + Rio, 1994-1996; cuid7808; 156713 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Red Hot 16, 1993-1996; cuid7809; 160516 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Royalty statements - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve, 1998 - 2003; cuid7810; 153976 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Sakamoto, Ryuichi, 1996; cuid7811; 156658 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Samples, 1996; cuid7812; 156590 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Skylab, 1996; cuid7813; 156703 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Stereolab, 1995-1996; cuid7814; 156705 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Stereolab, 1996; cuid7815; 156627 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Sting / Jobim, Antonio Carlos, 1995-1997; cuid7816; 156707 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Track by track, 1995-2000; cuid7817; 156599 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Veloso, Caetano, 1993; cuid7818; 156631 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Verve Records (Restricted), 1993-2000; cuid7819; 156603 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Video tracking log, bulk 1996; cuid7820; 151683 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Wheeler, Caron, 1996; cuid7821; 156711 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Wieden & Kennedy - Zima, 1998-1999; cuid7822; 156714 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Williams, Vanessa (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7823; 156708 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Williams, Vanessa (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7824; 156709 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Williams, Vanessa / Prince Charles Remix, 1996; cuid7825; 156706 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 138341
    - Cardboard ad - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7826; 161107 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Fliers - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7827; 161089 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Invitation envelope to Red Hot + Rio event, [n.d.]; cuid7828; 161098 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Invitation to Red Hot + Rio event, 1996; cuid7829; 161097 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Mossimo Music, in collaboration with Details magazine (Promotional), 1997; cuid7830; 161093 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Music You Haven't Heard Yet: Vol 2; Antilles Records (Promotional), 1996; cuid7831; 161092 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7832; 161094 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Press clippings (English), 1996 - 1997; cuid7833; 138342 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1996 - 1997; cuid7834; 138343 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles /Verve Records (Promotional), 1996; cuid7835; 161104 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Sticker ads - Red Hot + Rio, 1996; cuid7836; 161096 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Sticker buttons - Red Hot + Rio, [n.d.]; cuid7837; 161095 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161090
    - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve; PolyGram Records, 1996; cuid7838; 161100 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7839; 161106 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles /Verve Records, 1996; cuid7840; 161103 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Red Hot + Rio, Japanese edition; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7841; 161105 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Audio sound disc
    - Single (2 tracks): "The Boy from Ipanema," Crystal Waters; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7842; 161102 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Single (4 tracks): "The Boy from Ipanema," Crystal Waters; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996; cuid7843; 161101 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Series XI: Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 138314
  Silencio = Muerte: Red Hot + Latin was originally released in 1997 on Jellybean Benitez' H.O.L.A Recordings. In celebration of the album's ten-year anniversary, it was re-released in 2006 as Red Hot + Latin Redux by Nacional Records, featuring new bonus tracks and remastered tracks from the original release. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 151688
    - Advances from H.O.L.A Records (label), 1996; cuid7844; 153887 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7845; 155324 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Artist agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7846; 156557 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Aterciopelados, 1998; cuid7847; 154044 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7848; 151743 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Budget + Expenses (Restricted), 1996-1997; cuid7849; 155323 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Contact information, 1996-1997; cuid7850; 155327 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Cookman International, 1996; cuid7851; 155325 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Cost analysis, 1996 - 1999; cuid7852; 153960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Label agreements, 1996-1997; cuid7853; 156556 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Latin, 1996-1997; cuid7854; 155326 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Publishing, 1996-1997; cuid7855; 156555 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Samples, 1996; cuid7856; 156554 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Track by track, 1996-1997; cuid7857; 155322 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7858; 151689 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 138315
    - Flier ads - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997; cuid7859; 161112 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Postcard ads (big) - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997; cuid7860; 161114 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Postcard ads (small) - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997; cuid7861; 161110 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Press clippings (English), 1997; cuid7862; 138316 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1997; cuid7863; 138317 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional), 1996; cuid7864; 161120 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Café Tacuba and David Byrne, 1996; cuid7865; 161117 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Cibo Matto, 1996; cuid7866; 161119 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Geggy Tah, 1996; cuid7867; 161116 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by King Changó, 1996; cuid7868; 161118 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Simon Says, Volume Ten, Summer 1997; cuid7869; 161111 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Temporary tattoos - Silencio=Muerte, [n.d.]; cuid7870; 161122 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material, 160530
    - Slides: Album cover, [n.d.]; cuid7871; 160531 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161108
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records, 1996; cuid7872; 161121 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin CD liner notes, 1996; cuid7873; 161113 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Lain Redux; Nacional Records, 2006; cuid7874; 161123 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Series XII: Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute"), 1997; 151678
  Every Nation is a song composed by R. Kelly and included in the tribute album "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute." (Sony, 1997) Various artists contributed to the track, and they were collectively credited as "Red Hot R+B All Stars." (Reference: Amazon.com)
  - Subseries A: Production Files, 151679
    - Accounting, 1997; cuid7875; 153953 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Clearances (Restricted), 1997-1998; cuid7876; 157042 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Contracts (Restricted), 1997; cuid7877; 157041 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Di, Di, Di, 1997; cuid7878; 157043 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Evans, Faith, 1997; cuid7879; 157048 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Expenses etc. (Restricted), 1996-2000; cuid7880; 157044 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Video tracking log, 1997 - 1998; cuid7881; 151681 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 151680
    - Press clippings, 1997; cuid7882; 139225 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise, 161270
    - Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute; Sony, 1997; cuid7883; 161271 (Box 14, Folder 12)